### Aleksandra Kubicka

Senior Talent & EB Specialist at SentiOne | HR Business Partner

# Summary

I am relation-oriented, open-minded HR professional with about 4 years of experience in working for IT companies. I have wide knowledge and practical experience in broadly defined talent management - assessing staffing needs, end-to-end recruitment, supporting career development, rewarding, training and mentoring, creating motivation systems and overall management of talent growth. I have also defined and implement many HR processes, policies and strategies both in soft and hard HR area and ensured compliance with employment and labor laws. I have also been taking care of internal communication and Employer Branding in the companies I have cooperated with. To me, those activities are as important as the rest of HR tasks.

My psychological education, participation in various courses and constant willingness to learn provided me expertise to support managers and co-workers in conflict resolution, decision making or other everyday situations and simply do my job the best way possible.

In my professional and personal life, I am a big fan of Agile manifesto. When it comes to individuals and interactions, my relations with candidates, colleagues and friends are far more important than processes and tools. I always do my best to make sure everyone feels like home in the company and offer support and advice.

You can talk with me about your career development and opportunities or we can just meet for a coffee in our office to get to know each other better.

Let me know if you need anything from my side! aleksandra.kubicka@senti1.com

## Experience

Senior Talent & Employer Branding Specialist and Business Partner at SentiOne czerwiec 2017 - Present

- Co-creating and implementing HR strategies, processes and policies eg. company personnel policy, HRM system, recruitment and behavioural interviews procedures, onboarding new hires, offboarding, organizing feedback flow.
- Working closely with managers to accurately determine staffing needs.
- Managing full cycle recruitment processes for IT and non-IT positions: planning, organizing, interviewing, hiring, onboarding in Polish and European offices.

- Designing and implementing programs for evaluating employees, building career paths, and succession planning.
- Ensuring that HR processes comply with labor laws and company procedures.
- Supporting and mentoring managers in managing employee relations and conflict resolutions.
- Creating and conducting workshops for managers and employees.
- Creating and coordinating Employer Branding activities.
- Conducting surveys and analyzing results with validation, real improvements and follow-ups.
- Managing Internal communication.
- Being a guardian of company's' culture.

#### HR & Employer Branding Specialist at SolDevelo Sp. z o.o.

maj 2015 - maj 2017 (2 lata 1 miesiąc)

- Co-creating and implementing the company personnel policy.
- Designing and implementing programs from a scratch for evaluating employees, building career paths, onboarding, offboarding, engagement management etc.
- Working closely with founders to accurately determine staffing needs.
- Ensuring that HR processes comply with labor laws and company procedures.
- Managing full cycle recruitment processes for IT (Java Developers, PHP Developers, SysAdmins, Python Developers, Software Testers etc.) and non-IT positions, through sourcing candidates, running interviews to signing the contract.
- Supporting Team Leaders and managing employee relations, organizing feedback flow (eg. 1:1 meetings, quarterly evaluation meetings), coaching.
- Supporting creation of an organizational culture consistent with company values.
- Creating and coordinating Employer Branding activities.
- Managing Internal communication.
- Creating content and copywriting.
- Product Owner of the company website.

## IT Recruiter & Resourcer at ManpowerGroup Solutions

styczeń 2015 - maj 2015 (5 mies.)

- Recruitment for positions in IT, engineering and sales in the UK and Western European countries.
- Direct sourcing candidates using cold calling and persuasive techniques.
- Screening, testing, and qualifying candidates through the use of behavioral interviewing techniques and skill assessment testing.
- Proactively conducting research and investigate new ideas to find passive candidates through a variety of methods including Boolean search, social and professional networking groups.
- Developing an ongoing and diverse pipeline of prospective candidates.
- Conducting market researchers.

#### HR Administrator at Intel Corporation contracted by ManpowerGroup Solutions

#### listopad 2014 - styczeń 2015 (3 mies.)

- Administrative support of hiring processes.
- Cooperation with the recruitment units across the Europe.
- Pre-screening candidates.
- Managing candidates database in Taleo: uploading CV's, roles matching.
- Preparing reports.
- Supporting Employee Referral Program.
- Recruiting interns.

# Education

University of Gdansk

Master's degree, Organizational and Management Psychology, 2010 - 2015

# Aleksandra Kubicka

Senior Talent & EB Specialist at SentiOne | HR Business Partner



Contact Aleksandra on LinkedIn